(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ようこそ Welcome
Welcome
[ツノマキシステム]にログイン中...
Logging into [Tsunomaki System]...
パシワードを入力してください
Please enter a pashiword.
ketsu/hook
ツノマキシステム 起動します
Starting Tsunomaki System
わためいと専用パーソナルアシスタントAI
Personal Assistant AI for Watamates
ようこそ、watamate000001さま。
何かお手伝いできることはございますか？
Welcome, Watamate 000001. Is there anything I can help you with?
角巻わため 1st Anniversary Live Fever!! OP映像
Tsunomaki Watame 1st Anniversary Live Fever!! OP Movie
閲覧者が制限されています。
パスワードを入力してください。
Viewer restricted. Please enter password.
watame/did/nothing/wrong
再生しますか？
Play?
yes
2019.12.29 某所にて
2019.12.29 At a certain location
新時代のタレント。新メンバー、募集。
Next generation of talent. New members, recruiting.
Are you ready?
Turn the volume up!!
（ボーカル）
(Vocalizing)
あーあ またやっちゃった
Ah, I did it again
隠してたわけじゃないの
It's not that I was hiding it
もっとただ言っていたいだけ
I just want to keep saying it more
だって恥ずかしいんだもん
Because I'm embarrassed
意外と寂しん坊
Surprisingly a lonely heart
意外と甘えん坊
Surprisingly a spoiled child
Unexpectedly spoiled
意外と照れ屋
Unexpectedly shy
丸いソフトクリーム
Round soft-serve ice cream
飛び出したカップケーキ
A cupcake that popped out
3回目コンディショナー
Third time conditioner
甘まるパズル
Sweet and round puzzle
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢見心地
A fluffy, floating dreamlike state
ひとつひとつ数えておやすみなさい
Counting them one by one, good night
密かに芽生えたこの気持ち
This feeling that sprouted secretly
真っすぐ見つめないで
Don't look straight at me
...なんだっけ...
...What was it...
言葉にしちゃ時々そうじゃない
Putting it into words, sometimes it's not like that
照れちゃうだけじゃなくちゃじゃない
It's not just about being shy
ホントのホントは隠したいんじゃないの
The real truth isn't that I want to hide it
そうじゃないのにな
Even though it's not like that
Wow wow
曖昧なんじゃない
It's not ambiguous
この気持ちは間違いじゃない
This feeling is not a mistake
指切りげんまん
Pinky swear
かなり同時進行で
In a pretty parallel way
優柔不断でも
Even if I'm indecisive
絶対に毎日
Every single day
会いに来てくれるよね？
You'll come to see me, right?
本来臆病で
Naturally cowardly
案外泣き虫
Unexpectedly a crybaby
全然変わらずに
Without changing at all
元来キミばっか
Always only you
当たり前のようにキミがいないと
As if it's natural, if you're not here
ガッカリしちゃう
I'll be disappointed
ホントのホントにしょんぼりしちゃうわ
I'll really, truly get depressed
会いたくなっちゃうな
I'll end up wanting to see you
Wow wow
後悔ばっかじゃ
Just regrets
この心も勇気出しちゃえ
Let this heart take courage too
この指とまれ
Come and join me
みんなー！
Everyone!
今日は1周年記念配信にお越しくださり
Thank you so much for coming to the 1st anniversary stream today!
誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんなのおかげで1周年を迎えることができました！
Thanks to everyone, I was able to reach my 1st anniversary!
いつも本当に本当に支えてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for always really, really supporting me!
これからもよろしくね！
I look forward to your continued support!
楽しんでってください！
Please enjoy the show!
弱いところ気付かれたり
You notice my weak points
寂しさごと包まれたり
Being wrapped up along with my loneliness
いつまでも笑い合ったり
Laughing together forever
たまにはムッとケンカをしたり
Occasionally getting grumpy and fighting
ずっとずっとそばにいてほしい
I want you to be by my side forever and ever
約束だぞっ。
It's a promise.
言っちゃった
I said it
もしかしたら運命かも
Maybe it's destiny
赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
Maybe I can see the red thread of fate
ホントのホントはバレてるのかも
Maybe the real truth has been found out
目合わせらんないかも
Maybe I can't meet your eyes
Wow wow
曖昧なんてない
There's no ambiguity
たくさん私を見てて！
Look at me a lot!
言い切った
I've said it all
こんばんドドドー！
Good evening-dodo-do!
ホロライブ4期生、角巻わためです！
I'm Tsunomaki Watame of Hololive 4th Gen!
みんな、来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming!
なんと1周年を迎えましたー！
I have actually reached my 1st anniversary!
もうリハ頑張りすぎてヘトヘトなんだけど、
I'm already exhausted from working so hard on rehearsals, but...
頑張っていきたいなと思います！
I want to do my best!
そして今日は、こっち！
And today, use this!
#角巻わため1周年、こちらのハッシュタグでたくさんツイートしていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you could tweet a lot using the hashtag #TsunomakiWatame1stAnniversary!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
もう1発目は「愛昧ショコラーテ」だったんですけど、
The first song was 'Ai Mai Chocolate',
今日はドドドドドッて歌いますよ、いいですか？
but today I'm going to sing do-do-do-do-do, okay?
次の曲、行きますよ。
Let's go to the next song.
歌ってみた動画でも上げております。
I've also uploaded a cover video of this.
こういう場で初めて歌うかな。
This might be the first time I sing it at an event like this.
「ばぶるらぶ」
'Bubble Love'
世界はなんて複雑なんですか
Why is the world so complicated?
秘密の言葉教えてほしい
I want you to tell me the secret word
がんばれ私 いつも以上に
Good luck to me, more than usual
今日も明日も世界は回る
The world goes 'round today and tomorrow too
バブルラブ 作曲・作詞 : Junky
Bubble Love - Composition/Lyrics: Junky
今日も同じ日が来るなら いつも以上にしなくちゃって
If the same day comes again today,
I have to do more than usual.
会話ってああ難しい なんでも伝わるのに不器用
Conversations are so difficult;
everything gets through, yet I'm so clumsy.
何度も何度も頑張るのに
Even though I try over and over
できないこともあるかもなんて
I think maybe there are things I just can't do
そこで諦めなければいつかはきっと君まで届くから
If I don't give up there,
one day it will surely reach you
文字ならどうしても単純になっちゃいそうな感情は内緒の魔法唱えてほしい
Feelings that would somehow become simple if put into words...
I want you to chant a secret magic spell.
がんばれ私 時には大胆に
Good luck to me, sometimes be bold
今日も隣で世界を歩く
Today too, I walk the world by your side
実は怒るとこだったり嫉妬したりしちゃいます ハイ
Actually, I sometimes get angry or jealous, yes.
内緒な甘い魔法 見たこともないようなアイスクリーム
A secret sweet magic...
like an ice cream I've never seen before.
秘めた思いはドキドキドキ
Hidden feelings are pounding
溢れた言葉に真っ赤になって
I turn bright red at the words that overflow
みんなとうまく言えないけどそれでも一緒がいいな
I can't say it well with everyone,
but I still want to be together.
言葉はなんでこんなに困難で複雑なんですか秘密の言葉教えてほしい
Why are words so difficult and complicated?
I want you to tell me the secret word.
がんばれ私 いつも以上に
Good luck to me, more than usual
今日も明日も世界は回る
The world goes 'round today and tomorrow too
ずっとこれからも大好きなみんなと
From now on, forever with everyone I love
喧嘩したり仲直りしたりもっともっと
Fighting and making up... more and more
そんな平穏が続いていけばいいな
I hope that kind of peace continues
文字だと単純になっちゃいそうな感情は内緒の魔法を唱えてほしい
Feelings that would become simple in writing...
I want you to chant a secret magic spell.
がんばれ私 時には大胆に
Good luck to me, sometimes be bold
今日も隣で世界を歩かせて
Let me walk the world by your side today too
世界はなんて美しいんですか 秘密の言葉教えてほしい
Why is the world so beautiful?
I want you to tell me the secret word.
がんばれ私 いつも以上に
Good luck to me, more than usual
今日も明日も世界は回る
The world goes 'round today and tomorrow too
今日もみんなと世界を歩く
Today too, I walk the world with everyone.
おわり♪
The End♪
はー、イヤホンが外れちまったー
Phew, my earphone came off...
イヤホンないなった、片耳イヤホンないなった
My earphone's gone, my earphone for one ear is gone.
あった！
Found it!
ありがとうございましたー！ふー！
Thank you very much! Phew!
あぶねー、動きすぎた、最後にポロッと抜けてしもうたー
That was close... I moved too much,
it popped right out at the end.
あ、でも歌中じゃなくて良かったねー
Oh, but I'm glad it wasn't during the song.
あー、聴いてくれてありがとう。
Ah, thank you for listening.
これ「歌ってみた」動画も上げていて、
I've also uploaded a "covered it" video of this,
みんなにもね、すごい好きだよって言ってもらった曲だったから、
and since everyone told me they really liked it,
1周年で持ってきました。
I brought it here for the 1st anniversary.
聴いてくれてありがとう。
Thank you for listening.
次も、みんなに
Next is another song
わためのこの曲いいよって言われた曲です。
that everyone said "this song by Watame is great" about.
このまま聴いてください。
Please listen to it just as it is.
ハロ／ハワユ。
Hello/How are you.
ハロ
Hello
窓を開けて　小さく呟いた
Opening the window, I whispered softly
ハワユ
How are you
誰もいない　部屋で一人
In an empty room, all alone
モーニング
Morning
朝が来たよ　土砂降りの朝が
Morning has come, a morning of pouring rain
ティクタク
Tick-tock
私のネジを　誰か巻いて
Someone, please wind up my spring
ハロ／ハワユ
作曲・作詞：ナノウ
Hello/How are you
Music/Lyrics: Nanou
ハロ
Hello
昔のアニメにそんなのいたっけな
Was there someone like that in an old anime?
ハワユ
How are you
羨ましいな　みんなに愛されて
I'm so jealous, being loved by everyone
スリーピン
Sleepin'
馬鹿な事言ってないで支度をしなくちゃ
Stop talking nonsense and get ready
クライン
Cryin'
涙の跡を隠すため
To hide the traces of my tears
もう口癖になった「まあいっか」
It's become a habit to say "Oh well"
昨日の言葉がふと頭を過る
Yesterday's words suddenly cross my mind
「もう君には全然期待してないから」
"I'm not expecting anything from you anymore"
そりゃまあ私だって自分に期待などしてないけれど
Well, even I don't expect much from myself, but...
あれは一体どういうつもりですか
...what exactly did you mean by that?
喉元まで出かかった言葉
The words that almost came out of my throat
口を突いて出たのは嘘
The ones that actually came out were lies
こうして今日も私は貴重な
And so today as well, I continue to
言葉を浪費して生きてゆく
waste precious words as I live my life
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do you end up hiding it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Are you afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Do you not want to see anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
曖昧という名の海に溺れて
Drowning in a sea called ambiguity
息も出来ないほど苦しいの
It's so painful I can't even breathe
少し声が聞きたくなりました
I felt like I wanted to hear your voice a little
本当に弱いな
I'm really weak, aren't I?
一向に進まない支度の途中
In the middle of getting ready, making no progress
朦朧とした頭で思う
I think with a hazy head
「理由をつけて休んでしまおうかな」
"Maybe I'll just make up an excuse and take the day off"
いやいや分かってますって
No, no, I know...
なんとなく言ってみただけだよ
...I just felt like saying it
分かってるから怒らないでよ
I know, so don't get mad
幸せだろうと不幸せだろうと
Whether I'm happy or unhappy
平等に残酷に朝日は昇る
the sun rises equally and cruelly
生きていくだけで精一杯の私に
For me, who's doing my best just to keep living,
これ以上何を望むというの
...what more could you possibly ask?
何故気にしてしまうのですか
Why do you end up caring?
本当は愛されたいのですか
Do you actually want to be loved?
その手を離したのは誰ですか
Who was the one that let go of that hand?
気が付いていますか
Have you realized it yet?
人生にタイムカードがあるなら
If life had a time card,
終わりの時間はいつなんだろう
...when would the clock-out time be?
私が生きた分の給料は
The wages for the time I've lived,
誰が払うのですか
...who's going to pay them?
サンキュー　ありがとうって言いたいの
Thank you, I want to say thank you
サンキュー　ありがとうって言いたいよ
サンキュー　一度だけでもいいから
Thank you, even if it's just once
心の底から大泣きしながら　ありがとうって言いたいの
I want to say thank you while crying my heart out from the bottom of my soul
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do you end up hiding it?
本当は聞いて欲しいのですか
Do you actually want someone to listen?
絶対に笑ったりしないから
I promise I won't laugh,
話してみませんか
...so why don't you try talking to me?
口を開かなければ分からない
If you don't open your mouth, I won't know
思ってるだけでは伝わらない
Just thinking it won't get the message across
なんて面倒くさい生き物でしょう
What a troublesome kind of creature,
人間というのは
...humans are
ハロ　ハワユ
Hello, how are you
...ハロ、アユ
...Hello, how are you?
あなたに
To you,
ハロ、アユ
Hello, how are you?
あー
Ah...
ラララ...
La la la...
設定を見直して、クソザコ回線を卒業したので
I've reviewed my settings and graduated from my crappy internet connection,
歌、歌います！行きます！
so I'm going to sing! Here I go!
回線の設定を見直して
I reviewed the internet settings,
つよつよな回線になりました
and now I have a super strong connection.
もう絶対途切れ...
It'll never cut out again...
イエーイ！センキュー！
Yay! Thank you!
おなかすいた おなかすいた
I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
おいしいご飯が食べたいな
I want to eat delicious food.
あとさきなんにも考えないで
Without thinking about what comes next,
たくさん食べたいな
I want to eat a lot.
ほらほら顔上げ 叫べお前ら
Come on, look up and shout, everyone!
いつかに見捨てた 夢があるなら
If there's a dream that you once abandoned,
私めと 拾い集めよう
let's gather it up together with me.
ここから彼方へ 永久の止まぬ
From here to far away, eternally unceasing,
ほらほら顔上げ 叫べお前ら
come on, look up and shout, everyone!
すべて見落とすすくいなら
If it's a salvation that misses everything,
いっそ 夢物語でいいから
then I'd rather it be just a pipe dream.
例えばよく晴れた曇り空
For example, a perfectly clear cloudy sky,
キャンバスに見立てて思い描いた
likened to a canvas, on which I painted...
君の笑顔
your smile.
今は辛くても
Even if it's hard right now,
がむしゃらに叫んだ日々が
the days I spent shouting recklessly...
雲を破りやがて一筋の光
will break through the clouds, and eventually, a ray of light...
差し込んでくる
will come shining through.
青空の下で
Under the blue sky,
また君と
with you again,
出会いたい
I want to meet.
俺んとこ来ないか？
Won't you come to my place?
One Night Carnival 胸の奥
One Night Carnival, deep in my heart,
Zuki-Zukiと音立てるAngel
thumping and throbbing, Angel.
とにかくもう 行儀よく真面目なんて
Anyway, being well-behaved and serious...
うんざりだった Angel
I was sick of it, Angel.
アッフォー！
A-foo!
みんなも一緒に！
Everyone together!
アッフォー！
A-foo!
退屈に怯えてたのさ
I was terrified of boredom,
夜の闇に逃げ込んだAngel
escaping into the darkness of night, Angel.
捨て猫みたいな俺たちに
For us, who were like stray cats,
帰る場所なんて もうどこにもなかった Angel
there was no place left to return to, Angel.
Can you master baby
Master baby (A-foo!)
Be my baby (A-foo!)
Can you master baby ソロ！
Can you master baby, solo!
瞬きもせずに
Without even blinking,
俺たちは光の渦に
we are being drawn
巻き込まれてく
into a vortex of light.
雲の隙間に
In the gaps between the clouds,
照らせ 青白き月よ照らせ
shine! O pale moon, shine!
星が瞬くディスタンス
The distance where the stars twinkle,
寂しがり屋たちの伝説さ
it's the legend of the lonely ones.
One Night Carnival Funky!
みんなー！楽しんでってください！
Everyone! Please enjoy yourselves!
風に香る微かな苦沙
A faint bitterness scented in the wind
俺の胸を締め付けるAngel
Tightens my heart, Angel
焼けたアスファルトに這った鼓動は
The heartbeat crawling on the scorched asphalt
確かに俺たちは聞いたんだ
We certainly heard it
Angel Can You Master Baby
Master Baby
Can You Master Baby
Can You Master Baby Be My Baby
Can You Master Baby Solo
So So So...
俺たちがハサグレたことに
There was no reason for us
理由なんてなかったよ
to go astray.
ただ少しだけ
Maybe we were just
不器用だったのかもしれない
a little bit clumsy.
恋しているのさ
I'm in love
この夜に恋してるのさ
I'm in love with this night
やがて海が見える
Soon the sea will be visible
寂しがり屋たちの
The legend of
伝説さ
the lonely ones
One Night Carnival Fun Fun
あの頃の俺たち
Back then,
闇の中じゃなきゃ夢見られなかった
we couldn't dream unless we were in the darkness.
あのミラーボールみたいに
Just like that mirror ball,
明るくてまんまるのお月さんに憧れただけさ
we just longed for the bright, round moon.
行こうぜ！
Let's go!
ピリオドの向こうへ！
To the other side of the period!
もうすぐ海が見える
Soon the sea will be visible
寂しがり屋たちの
The legend of
伝説さ
the lonely ones
One Night Carnival Fun Fun
One Night Carnival Oh No
Let's Get Free
いぇーい！
Yay!
最高のワンナイトカーニバルだったよな！
That was the best One Night Carnival, wasn't it!
あとステージが、これ
Also, the stage...
ナイトフィーバーのステージに変わりました！
It changed to the Night Fever stage!
そして後ろには
And behind me,
桐生ココの舎弟、ちょっと今日はお借りしております。
I'm borrowing Kiryu Coco's underlings for a bit today.
あっ、一緒に後ろ向いちゃうんだね（笑）
Oh, you all turned around too (lol).
お借りしております！
I'm borrowing them!
あと、さっきのワンナイトカーニバルなんだけど
Also, about that One Night Carnival just now,
コーラスを、えっと、とある方々にお願いをしまして
I asked certain people to do the chorus...
誰か分かったかな？
I wonder if anyone realized who?
分かったかな？
Did you figure it out?
声だいぶ特徴あったと思うんだけど
I think their voices were quite distinctive,
実は
but actually,
5期生のみんなにお願いしました！
I asked the Gen 5 members!
ポルカちゃん、ねねちゃん
Polka-chan, Nene-chan,
ラミィちゃん、ししろ
Lamy-chan, Shishiro.
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
そして、次の曲は
And for the next song,
バカタレ共にコーラスをお願いしております！
I've asked Bakatare to do the chorus!
ちょっと水飲んでもいい？
Can I drink some water for a second?
お水いただきまして
I'll have some water...
くぅ～！
Ahhh!
染みる～！
It hits the spot!
染み渡る～（笑）
It's soaking in (lol).
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
では行きましょう。
Now then, let's go.
次の曲みんなもダンスするんだぞ。
Everyone, dance along to the next song too.
キングゲイナー！
King Gainer!
キングキングキングゲイナー！
KING KING KING GAINER!
キングゲイナー・オーバー！
KING GAINER OVER!
作曲：田中公平 作詞：井荻麟
Comp: Kohei Tanaka Lyrics: Rin Iogi
キェー！キングゲイナー！
Kyehh! KING GAINER!
メタオーバーマン キングゲイナー！
METAL OVERMAN KING GAINER!
真っ白い地平の向こうから
From beyond the pure white horizon
あいつの影が
His shadow
俺を呼ぶんだ
calls out to me
一人だけでは何ができると...
What can I do alone?...
いじける俺に教えてくれた
You showed me, as I was moping
君と出会って 胸を合わせば
When I met you and our hearts aligned
命が
My life...
メタルファイアー 燃えてきた
Metal Fire, I'm burning up
メタルファイアー
Metal Fire
コォォォォ！
Goooo!
キング、キング、キングゲイナー！
King, King, King Gainer!
ダンス、ダンス、ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance!
キングゲイナー！
King Gainer!
キング、キング、キングゲイナー！
King, King, King Gainer!
愛と勇気は言葉
Love and courage are words
感じられれば力
If you can feel them, they become strength
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
探すのさ 今 ここで
I'll search for it, right here, right now
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
メタルオーバーマン キングゲイナー！
Metal Overman, King Gainer!
ダンス、ダンス、ダンス、ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance, dance!
シェイク・ユア・ボディ、シェイク・ユア・ボディ！
Shake your body, shake your body!
今日はパリナイだぞ！踊れ！
It's a party night today! Dance!
みんなみんなダンスありがとう！
Everyone, thanks for the dancing!
キング、キング、キングゲイナー！
King, King, King Gainer!
凍てつく吹雪を切り裂いて
Cutting through the freezing blizzard
奴に遅れず 飛んで見せたい
Without falling behind him, I want to show I can fly
明日という日覗きたいから
Because I want to peek into tomorrow
おじける俺を忘れるために
To forget my cowering self
抱かせてくれよ お前の心
Let me hold your heart
命を
My life...
メタルファイアー 愛してる
Metal Fire, I love you
メタルファイアー
Metal Fire
コォォォォ！
Goooo!
愛と勇気は口先だけの
If love and courage are just
事とわかれば求め合え
Lip service, then let's seek each other
キング、キング、キングゲイナー！
King, King, King Gainer!
みんなも一緒に！
Everyone together!
キング、キング、キングゲイナー！
King, King, King Gainer!
ダンス、ダンス、ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance!
キングゲイナー！
King Gainer!
一人だけでは嫌だ
I don't want to be alone
お前だけでも無理だ
And it's impossible with just you
愛と勇気は言葉
Love and courage are words
感じられれば力
If you can feel them, they become strength
一人だけでは嫌だ
I don't want to be alone
お前だけでも無理だ
And it's impossible with just you
愛と勇気は言葉
Love and courage are words
感じられれば力
If you can feel them, they become strength
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
探すのさ 今 ここで
I'll search for it, right here, right now
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
メタルオーバーマン キングゲイナー！
Metal Overman, King Gainer!
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
今懸ける この命
I'm betting my life on this moment
イェイ！
Yay!
キ、キ、キングゲイナー
Ki, Ki, King Gainer
メタルオーバーマン キングゲイナー！
Metal Overman, King Gainer!
Thank you!
うっ、はは、あっちー！
Whew, haha, so hot!
水飲んでもいいですか？
Can I drink some water?
これリハでさ、ずっと歌ってたらさ、
During the rehearsal, I sang it so many times
もう力尽きちゃってさ
that I ran out of strength.
うめー！
Delicious!
そして、残念ながら、
And unfortunately,
あの後ろのヤクザさんとはここでお別れになります。
this is where we part ways with the yakuza guys behind me.
一緒に水飲んでくれてありがとう。
Thank you for drinking water with me.
♪キングゲイナー・オーバー！
♪King Gainer Over!
#角巻わため1周年
#Watame1stAnniversary
じゃあね！バイバイ！
See ya! Bye-bye!
ありがとね！一緒に踊ってくれてありがとう！
Thanks! Thank you for dancing with me!
すーっと...
Just like that...
すーっと消えていく。
They just vanish away.
ありがとう。みんなも一緒に踊ってくれたり、あの、
Thank you. Thanks to everyone for dancing along and, uh,
キン、キングゲイナーって言ってくれたり、
saying "King... King Gainer,"
ありがとう！
thank you!
とっても楽しかったで。
I had so much fun.
次もみんなに、あの、意外と、あの、
Next, I'd like to sing a song that everyone said,
「この曲合うかも」って言ってもらった曲を
"This song might actually suit you well."
歌いたいなと思います。
I hope you enjoy it.
吉原ラメント。
Yoshiwara Lamento.
吉原ラメント
作詞・作曲：亜沙
Yoshiwara Lamento
Lyrics/Composition: Asa
江戸の町は今日も深く　夜の帳（とばり）下りて行く
Today as well, the town of Edo is being deeply covered by the veil of night
鏡向いて紅を引いて　応（おう）じるまま　受け入れるまま
Facing the mirror, applying rouge, accepting and submitting as told
橙（だいだい）色　輝いた花　憧れてた　望んでた
The orange-glowing flower I yearned for and desired
いつの間にか藍色の花　けれど私　安くないわ
Before I knew it, it became an indigo flower, but I am not cheap
真（まこと）はただ一人のどなたかのためだけに咲いていたかったのだけれど
Truthfully, I wanted to bloom for only one person, however...
運命はわっちの自由奪い、そいで歯車を回していくのでありんす
Fate stole my freedom and continues to turn the gears
偽りだらけの恋愛　そして私を抱くのね
Love full of lies, and so you embrace me
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原　今日は雨
Pretending to feel to a sad degree, it's raining in Yoshiwara again today
貴方様どうか私を　買っていただけないでしょうか
My lord, won't you please buy me?
咲き出す傘の群れに　濡れる私は雨
Wet among the crowd of blooming umbrellas, I am the rain
行き交う群れ　賑わう声が　ひしめき合い　愛を連れて
The passing crowds, the bustling voices, jostling together and bringing love
願うことはどうかいつか　鳥籠の外　連れ出して
My only wish is that someday you'll take me out of this birdcage
真（まこと）は行く宛てなど無くなってしまいましたのだけれど
Truthfully, I have nowhere left to go, however...
こなたの籠の中から見える景色だけは、まっちい何時の時も癒してくれるのでありんす
The scenery from within this cage always truly heals my soul
偽りだらけの恋愛　そして私を買うのね
Love full of lies, and so you buy me
私に咲いた花びら　濡れる心にふるわ雨
The petals that bloomed on me, it's raining on my wet heart
貴方様どうか私と　一夜限りの戯（たわむ）れを
My lord, won't you please share a single night's play with me?
望む染みの数が　鈍く心に刺さる
The number of stains I desire pierces my heart dully
憂い帯びた花　望む　果てる
The melancholy flower desires to come to an end
ようこそおいでくんなまし
Welcome, please come in
恋人ごっこの夜に　吐息あとなかせて
On this night of playing lovers, let your sighs ring out
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原　今日は雨
Pretending to feel to a sad degree, it's raining in Yoshiwara again today
偽りだらけの恋愛　そして私を抱くのね
Love full of lies, and so you embrace me
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原　今日は雨
Pretending to feel to a sad degree, it's raining in Yoshiwara again today
貴方様どうか私を　買っていただけないでしょうか
My lord, won't you please buy me?
咲き出す傘の群れに　濡れる私は雨
Wet among the crowd of blooming umbrellas, I am the rain
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
やっぱこういうなか綺麗な場所だとさ、
After all, being in a beautiful place like this
緊張するね（笑）
makes me nervous (haha).
水飲んでいいですか？
Can I drink some water?
いや次の曲がね、大変なもんでね。
Well, the next song is quite a tough one.
ふごっ！
Fugo!
あ、今、今ちょっと「ふごっ」て音が入ってしまいました。
Ah, just now... a "fugo" sound got picked up.
すみませんでした。
I'm sorry.
ふごふごしてしまいました。
I ended up making a "fugo-fugo" sound.
いや次...次がね、もうね...
Well, next... the next one is...
すごいよ
It's amazing!
すごいですよ
It's really amazing!
頑張りましたよ
I worked hard for this!
じゃ、行きましょうか
Well, shall we get started?
もう一番盛り上がるところだと言ってもいい
You could even say this is the most exciting part.
最高に盛り上がってください
Please get as hyped as possible!
たくさんコメントもください
Please leave lots of comments too!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
L.L.L.!
Don't you give me your love and passion?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
L.L.L. 作詞・作曲: MYTH & ROID
L.L.L. Lyrics & Composition: MYTH & ROID
迷彩のHELL 忠実なGUARD
Camouflaged hell, faithful guard
一瞬も白も知る死に体じゃない
Not a corpse that knows a moment or light
GUARD LINE 果てない 焦らんでご覧
The guard line is endless, look, don't be impatient
SPARKY GRAPH ON THE SYMBOL
あなたは守護 真に言うなら忠実にFOLLOW
You are the protection, follow faithfully if I speak truly
GIVE AND TAKE 私の支配
Give and take, my dominion
何より尊いものよ
It's more precious than anything else
YOU DON'T KNOW WHY 今さらなSTYLE
You don't know why, this belated style
偽着臭い 過剰なCRY
Smells of fake attachment, an excessive cry
問い合いたい どんな暗い
I want to ask, no matter how dark
嫉妬もサクリファイスよ
Even jealousy is a sacrifice
DON'T YOU GIVE ME YOUR LOVE AND PASSION?
会いたい衝動がRED LINE
The urge to see you is at the red line
ココロ以上にホンノウ ハテまで燃え尽くしたい
Instinct over heart, I want to burn out to the end
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE ONE MORE WITH WITHOUT YOU
あなた以外この未来は
Other than you, this future is...
キリ キリ I'D BE HAPPY KILLING FOR MY LOVE
Kiri Kiri, I'd be happy killing for my love
強靭なCASE 視線はLOCK
Tough case, gaze is locked
遮れずにとろけたい願い
A wish to melt away without obstruction
SHAPE OF YOUR 精神はFLY
The shape of your spirit is flying
あぶんでそらす SPARKY BUTTERFLY ON HELL
Deflecting with fire, sparky butterfly on hell
GET OUT じゃない 視界の端 排除してたい
It's not 'Get out', I want to eliminate the edge of my vision
切ってもよし 容赦などない
Even if I cut, there is no mercy
誰より譲れぬものよ
It's something I won't yield to anyone
AMAZED な 景色に合致
Matching the amazed scenery
眩めない 鼓動会いたい
Not blinding, I want to meet your heartbeat
共にいたい 飲みたい
I want to be together, I want to drink
嫉妬もサクリファイスよ
Even jealousy is a sacrifice
WON'T YOU COME AND HOLD ME TIGHT?
会いたい純情結晶化
The pure heart that wants to meet crystallizes
想像以上のオンジョウ ハードな個体要望して
Beyond imagination, requesting a hard solid body
I WANNA BE WITH YOU BABY
あなたの愛を得られるなら
If I can have your love
RISKY RISKY I'M GONNA RISKY ALL FOR MY LOVE
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
狂愛の模様 眩醒を介して
Pattern of mad love, through awakening
ワインドゆご 焦燥細胞
Winding, anxious cells
刑場は密葬 自由に細胞単位で
Execution ground is a secret burial, freely by cell unit
DON'T YOU GIVE ME YOUR LOVE AND PASSION?
あなたのすべて頂戴
Give me everything of yours
理由なんていらない ただ愛し愛されたい
I don't need a reason, I just want to love and be loved
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE ONE MORE WITH WITHOUT YOU
あなた以外何もいらない
I don't need anything but you
GET IT GET IT I CAN'T RESIST GETTING FOR MY LOVE
I SPEND MY LIFE FOR LOVING YOU
キリ キリ
Kiri kiri
IMAGINE THAT IN MY EXTRA PARADISE
SAY HEAVEN WAS ONLY ME FOR ALL MY LIFE
MY LIFE HELD THIS IN THE END
DON'T YOU GIVE ME YOUR LOVE AND PASSION?
I LIKE ABOUT YOUR SHIVERING LEG
Thank you.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
水を飲みまーす！
I'm going to drink some water!
お水、お水...
Water, water...
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
や、これ、これリハでめっちゃ歌ってさ
Man, I sang this so many times in rehearsal...
2回リハで全力で歌ってさ
...sang it with everything I had twice in rehearsal...
もうヘトヘトなんじゃが、何とか歌えてよかったです
...and I'm already exhausted, but I'm glad I managed to sing it somehow.
どう？楽しかった？かっこよかった？
How was it? Did you have fun? Was it cool?
実はこの後もまだありますんで
Actually, there's still more after this,
ありますんで、このまま見てて下さい。ビッグニュースありますんで
so please keep watching. I have some big news coming up.
パチパチいっぱいありがとう！
Thank you for all the applause!
スパチャもね、メンバーシップも本当にありがとうございます
Thank you so much for the Super Chats and memberships too.
見えてますよ！ありがとう！
I see them! Thank you!
では...
Well then...
なんかね、今日ね、
You know, today,
あの、ホロライブENのね、
well, from Hololive English,
カリオペちゃんからメッセージをいただいております。
I've received a message from Calliope-chan.
メッセージ、どうぞ！
Here's the message!
こんにちは、おす、カリオペ・モリです。
Hello! Yo, I'm Mori Calliope.
わため先輩、1周年おめでとうございます！
Watame-senpai, happy 1st anniversary!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こういうレベル特別の曲に誘ってくれて
Thank you for inviting me to such a special song.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
今回はね、素晴らしい曲になりましたね。
This time, it's become a wonderful song.
すごい。本当に本当によかったです。
Amazing. I'm really, really glad.
わため先輩の声が大好きなので、
I love Watame-senpai's voice, so...
至極光栄です。
it's a great honor.
イェーイ、
Yay,
これからもよろしくお願いします。
I look forward to working with you.
またいつか誘ってくださいね。
Please invite me again sometime.
またいつかね、あの、何か作りたいと思いますね、
I'd like to make something again someday,
一緒に。うんうん。
together. Yeah.
Let's make a nice song together again someday.
Thank you so much for inviting me,
and congrats on one year anniversary!
Woo! Yay!
Anyway, thank you so much and おめでとうございます。
Anyway, thank you so much and congratulations.
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ここからは、ちょっと喋らせてもらってもいいですか？
From here on, may I talk a bit?
なんとカリオペちゃんからメッセージをいただいたのも、
I received a message from Calliope-chan, and...
なんとこの後、
what's more, after this,
21時15分、9時15分、PM 9:15から...
at 21:15, 9:15, 9:15 PM...
なんとカリオペちゃんとコラボした、
I'm collaborating with Calliope-chan!
あ、カリオペちゃんいる、ありがとう！ありがとう！
Oh, Calliope-chan is here! Thank you! Thank you!
なんとコラボしまして、しかも、
We've collaborated! And,
「曇天羊」を feat. カリオペちゃんで
we've made 'Cloudy Sheep' feat. Calliope-chan...
フル作成いたしました！
the full version!
この後、9時15分から動画が上がります！
The video will be uploaded after this at 9:15!
サムネかっこいい！
The thumbnail is so cool!
しかも、あの、ダンスPVとなっておりまして、
Also, it's a dance PV.
あの、ダンスをね、ちょっと頑張らせてもらって、
I worked hard on the dance,
撮影して、それをかっこいい動画にしていただいたので、
filmed it, and had it made into a cool video.
是非、この後9時15分、動画を見ていただきたいなと思います！
So please watch the video at 9:15 after this!
プレミア公開するので、お願いします。
It'll be a premiere, so please join us.
多分ね、概要欄とかにね、
I think they'll put the link in the description,
この後記載してきてくれると思うんだけど、見てね！
but please watch it!
「曇天羊」オリジナル、角巻わため feat. カリオペです。
'Cloudy Sheep' Original, Tsunomaki Watame feat. Calliope.
お願いします。
Please check it out.
そして、1周年といえば、
And speaking of a 1st anniversary,
みんな出してるあれがあるわよね、記念のあれがよ。
there's that thing everyone releases, right?
記念、グッズ！
Anniversary goods!
ワオ！
Wow!
活動1周年記念グッズ！
1st Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
ふーみママ描き下ろし、ラバーマット？
A rubber mat drawn by Fumi-mama?
わためナイトフィーバー、ストーンコースター？
Watame Night Fever stone coaster?
あ、なんだ、角巻わためファースト、なんだ？
Oh, what's this? Tsunomaki Watame 1st, what?
あ、なになになに、これなんだ？
Oh, what's this?
ちょっと後で説明するからよ。順番にいこう。
I'll explain it later. Let's go in order.
では、画像お願いします。
Now, pictures please.
ジャジャーン！ふーみ先生描き下ろし、ラバーマット！
Ta-da! A rubber mat drawn by Fumi-sensei!
いやこれさ、あの、たぶんビッグサイズで見たら
I think you'll see if you look at it in a large size.
わかるんじゃないかな。なんか穿いてないのでは？
Is she not wearing anything?
あれ？これ、下穿いてますかね？
Wait... is she wearing anything underneath?
へへっ。
Hehe.
ふーみママに聞いたらね、なんのこと？って言ってた。
I asked Fumi-mama and she said 'What are you talking about?'.
え、なんのこと？ってとぼけてたけどね、ははっ。
She was playing dumb, haha.
そう、ラバーマット。ラバーマットっていうのは、
Yes, a rubber mat. A rubber mat is...
机の上とかに敷く、ちょっとデッカいサイズの、
a large mat you put on your desk.
サイズも書いてあったと思うんだけど、敷けるマットになっております。
I think the size was written there, too.
で、わためナイトフィーバー、ストーンコースター。あの、コースターね。
And the Watame Night Fever stone coaster. That coaster.
ちょっと、また別バージョンで、珪藻土じゃないんだけど、
It's a different version, not diatomaceous earth...
ちょっと別バージョンで作っていただいたので、これも一緒に届きます。
but a different version, so this will be included too.
あと特典がありまして。
And there's a bonus.
そう、穿いてない、ザワザワ。
Yes, 'she's not wearing anything', buzz buzz.
画像お願いします。特典がね、あるんですよ。
Pictures please. There's a bonus!
ババーン！ふーみママ描き下ろし、角巻わため、
Bam! Drawing by Fumi-mama, Tsunomaki Watame,
箔押し複製サイン入りイラストポストカード！
foil-stamped replica signature illustration postcard!
これがさっきのラバーマットで、両目が開いてたと思うんだけど、
In the rubber mat from before, both eyes were open...
あの、ウインクしております、こっち。へへっ。
but in this one, I'm winking. Hehe.
ウインクさせてもらいました！いやいやいや。
I got to wink! No way.
あと、特典ボイス1種。あ、なんたら、なんたら制作秘話。
Also, one type of bonus voice. Oh, the production story.
あ、わためのね、ボイスもついてきます！
My voice will be included too!
では、行きましょうか。
Shall we get started?
画像、お願いします。
Images, please.
角巻わため 1stアルバム『わためのうた』vol.1!
Tsunomaki Watame's 1st Album "Watame no Uta" Vol. 1!
声でかくなっちゃうんだ。
My voice is getting loud.
ホロライブ4期生、角巻わための1年間の軌跡を詰め込んだ珠玉のファーストアルバムです。
It's a gem of a first album, packed with a year's worth of Tsunomaki Watame's journey as a Hololive 4th generation member.
もう本当にギリギリのギリギリで、あのね、グッズとか制作班の方とかに、もうめちゃくちゃお世話になりまして。
It was really down to the wire, and I'm so indebted to the goods and production teams.
今もなお、多分お世話になってると思うんだけど、本当にありがとうございます。
I'm probably still relying on them now, but thank you so much.
夢が1つ、また叶いました。
Another dream has come true.
ありがとうございます、本当に。
Thank you, really.
本当にこうやって配信できるのもね、今、動いてくださってね、スタジオで頑張ってくださってる方もおかげでもあるので...
Being able to stream like this is also thanks to the people working hard in the studio right now...
運営さん本当にありがとう。マネちゃんもありがとう。ふーみママもありがとう。
Management, thank you so much. Mane-chan, thank you. Fumi-mama, thank you.
けー、けぴパパもありがとう。ゆうじさんもありがとう。わためぇともありがとう！
Ke- Kepi-papa, thank you too. Yuji-san, thank you. Watamate, thank you too!
みんなの応援があったから形になりました。
It took shape because of everyone's support.
うぅ、あかん、泣いたらあかんで。
Ugh, no, I shouldn't cry.
なんと、クソザコ回線の、ま、ちょこちょこと作ってきた曲とか、「愛昧ショコラーテ」とか、「曇天羊」とか...
And, songs I've made here and there with my "trash internet", like "Ai-mai Chocolate", "Donten Hitsuji"...
あとスペシャル・トラックもなんと付いてきます、1曲。
And there's even a special track included!
よかったら、全部セットでしか買えないんだけど、
If you'd like, you can only get it in the full set,
特典という形なんだけど、夢が叶いましたので、よかったら買ってほしいなと思います。
but it's a dream come true, so I'd love for you to buy it.
あと、vol.1っていうのも、vol.2出せたらいいなっていう思いを込めて、
Also, I named it Vol. 1 with the hope that I'll be able to release Vol. 2 one day,
vol.1を付けました。
so I added the "Vol. 1".
やぁ、夢を叶える羊じゃーい！
Yeah, I'm the sheep who makes dreams come true!
これからも夢をどんどん叶えていきたいと思いますので、応援をよろしくお願いいたします。
I want to keep making more and more dreams come true, so please continue to support me.
いやぁ、やっと言えたよ。やっと言えた。
Wow, I finally said it. I finally said it.
匂わせないように頑張った。やっと言えた。
I tried so hard not to hint at it. I finally said it.
こちらこそありがとうだよ。
No, thank YOU.
みんながね、こうやって応援してくれてるおかげで形になりましたよ。
It's thanks to all of you supporting me like this that it's taken shape.
CDだよ！来年2出したいですね。
A CD! I want to release Vol. 2 next year.
だから2年目もどうぞよろしくお願いいたします。
So please support me in my second year as well.
一生懸命ボイトレも頑張ります。
I'll do my best with vocal training.
ダンスも頑張ります。
I'll do my best with dancing.
配信も頑張ります。お願いします。
I'll do my best with streaming. Please!
で、なんとこの後ですね、カリオペちゃんと一緒に歌わせてもらう「曇天羊」、歌わせてもらおうかなと。
And, what's more, next I'll be singing "Donten Hitsuji" with Calliope-chan.
いや、ここで歌っても動画見てよ。
Well, I'm singing it here, but please watch the music video too.
頼むよ。ダンス頑張ったんだから動画も見てよ。
I beg you. I worked hard on the dance, so watch the video too.
先行で聞かせ、き、き、聞いてもらいたいなと思います。
I'd like to let you hear it, it's a preview.
「曇天羊」角巻わため feat. カリオペ、聴いてください。
"Donten Hitsuji", Tsunomaki Watame feat. Calliope. Please listen.
例えばよく晴れた曇り空
For instance, a cloudy sky that's clearly bright
キャンバスに見立てて今僕は
I'm treating it like a canvas now
何を描こう
What shall I paint?
下ろしたての靴で走り出す
Running out in brand-new shoes
道とも呼べぬ獣道
A beastly trail that can't even be called a path
汚れてしまうことを恐れてちゃ
If you're afraid of getting dirty
どこにも行けないんだってね
You won't be able to go anywhere, you know
良くない天気に顔伏せ歩いて
Walking with my face down in bad weather
全て見落とすくらいなら
If I'm going to miss out on everything
いっそ夢物語でいいから
I'd rather it be just a dream
例えばよく晴れた曇り空
For instance, a cloudy sky that's clearly bright
キャンバスに見立てて思い描いた
I imagined it as a canvas
君の笑顔を
And painted your smile
今は辛くてもがむしゃらに
Even if it's hard now, I'll keep going recklessly
叫んだ日々が雲を破り
The days I spent shouting will break through the clouds
やがて一筋の光
And eventually, a single ray of light
差し込んでくる青空の下で
Will shine down, under the blue sky
また君と
Once again, with you
振り返れば全ての思い出が
Looking back, all those memories
色鮮やかとは呼べない
I can't exactly call them vivid
涙で滲みボロボロになってる
They're blurred with tears and worn to tatters
ページがいくつも
On so many pages...
♪ 曇天羊 feat. カリオペ
♪ Kumotenyou feat. Calliope
...終わるよ
...it'll end.
The higher they climb, the harder they fall
And now at last I finally say goodbye
To the friendless and shy once upon a time me
In an endless suspense, the sky has been here all along
Same song in my heart, no fear be it low or high
It's time do or die, writing in the sky the story that starts with you and I
ふっと白い絵具があれば
If I had a sudden splash of white paint,
どんな高いペンがあれば
If I had any expensive pen,
世界で一番の絵が描けるって
Thinking I could draw the best picture in the world—
そんなわけないから
That's just not how it works.
一つ 二つ また一つ 線を描いた
One, two, and another line I drew.
少し また少しずつ
Little by little, bit by bit,
増えていく 景色が
the scenery grows.
君といた 景色が
The scenery of when I was with you.
僕が好きな 一番好きな色
My favorite, my most favorite color.
二度と会えない日が来たとしても
Even if the day comes when we can't meet again,
少しでも長く覚えていたい
I want to remember it for as long as possible.
君といた日 その歌声
The days with you, that singing voice.
全部 全部 夢物語じゃないから
Because all of it, all of it, is not just a dream.
例えば よく晴れた曇り空
For example, a bright cloudy sky,
キャンバスに見立てて思い描いた
I imagined it as a canvas—
君の笑顔
your smiling face.
今は辛くても
Even if it's hard right now,
がむしゃらに叫んだ日々が
the days when I screamed recklessly
雲を破りやがて 一筋の光
will break the clouds and soon, a ray of light
差し込んでくる 青空の下で
will shine through. Under the blue sky,
また君と 出会いたい
I want to meet you again.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はー、もうやりきったよ。
Phew, I really gave it my all.
わー、みんな聴いてくれてありがとう。
Wow, thank you everyone for listening.
あと、わためいとのみんな、来てくれてありがとう。
Also, to all the Watamates, thank you for coming.
駆けつけてくれて、いつもありがとうね。
Thank you for rushing here, as always.
支えられています。本当にありがとう。
I feel so supported. Truly, thank you.
そして、この時間を空けてくれたホロメンのみんなもありがとう。
And thank you to all the Hololive members who made time for this.
先輩も後輩も、
Seniors, juniors,
同期も、みんなありがとう。
and my gen-mates—thank you all.
今回、みんな忙しいかなと思って、同期にはちょっと声をかけるのを遠慮してしまったんだけど、次は、あの、声をかけようと思います。
This time, thinking everyone might be busy, I hesitated to ask my gen-mates, but next time, I'll be sure to reach out.
本当に、5期生のみんなも、バカタレ共も、しらけんも、時間取って録音してくれてありがとう。
Truly, thank you to the 5th gen, the Bakatare group, and the Shiraken members for taking the time to record for me.
みんなありがとう本当に。
Thank you all, really.
この後、ふー、21時15分からプレミアム公開あります。
After this, phew, there's a premiere at 9:15 PM.
カリオペちゃんもありがとうね。
Thank you, Calliope-chan.
ダンスも歌も頑張りました。よかったらプレミアム公開見てください。お願いします。
I worked hard on the dancing and singing. Please check out the premiere if you can. I'm counting on you.
そしてグッズ、ラバーマット、あとコースター、特典ポストカード、ボイス、なんといってもアルバム！
And the merch! Rubber mats, coasters, bonus postcards, voice packs, and most importantly, the album!
ちょっと、あの、1枚別売りにはできなかったんだけど、あの、まるっとね、買ってもらえたらすごく嬉しいなと思います。
I couldn't sell them individually, but I'd be so happy if you bought the whole set.
そして、その買ってくれたものを糧に、買ってくれたみんなの気持ちを糧に、来年ますます頑張って夢を叶えていきたいなと思いますので、どうぞよろしくお願いいたします！
And using your support and the merch you bought as my strength, I'll work even harder next year to make my dreams come true, so please continue to support me!
これで1周年を迎えられたのもみんなのおかげです！ありがとうございました！ありがとう！またね！
I've reached my 1st anniversary all thanks to you! Thank you so much! Thank you! See you!
角巻わため 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!
Tsunomaki Watame 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!
【 #角巻わため1周年 】角巻わため 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!🌟【ホロライブ４期生】
[#Watame1stAnniversary] Tsunomaki Watame 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!🌟 [Hololive 4th Generation]